Hello friends, I am your
friend, your friend, your advisor
Nandkishore Tiwari. Friends, today I am here to discuss
Policy Bazaar, a
brand new platform for point of sales
persons. Friends, as I have already
made a video and given it to you earlier, Policy
Bazaar, which used to be a great insurance company, has
left its web edition business and has become Polished Bazaar
Insurance Broker Private Limited,
through which you get an insurance
broker and along with this insurance
broker, which is the biggest insurance intermediary complaint of ₹1,
you get a very good property,
here you can get a golden opportunity to share the product of all the insurance companies presented by
Bankhedi Polish Promotion, a partner of Polished Bazaar, which is
more than 65,000,000,
you are getting a golden opportunity to share the product of Suresh Life and General Insurance Company.
Friends, I am very happy to inform you
that on this platform of Policy Bazaar,
more than 25 thousand partners
and more than 30 partners are
doing this work very fast. Friends,
now it is your turn, if you want to make a strong contribution in your life.  If you
want to create a strong income stream,
you can learn more about passive income and active investment by
watching our videos. So,
if you
want to see a truly remarkable opportunity for your life, then PolicyBazaar's
Point of Sales
Person (POS) is also called a Scorpio SP. Firstly,
this will prove to be a milestone for you.
Friends, if you become a PolicyBazaar partner,
you will have the opportunity to share all the products available on the PolicyBazaar portal. By using this,
you can increase
your income tenfold
to fourfold in the coming years.
Secondly, friends,
you don't have to invest or
explain even a single rupee to do all this. Point number three,
friends, our team provides
you with the best target base
specifications, excellent training, and the best
product guidelines every week and every month.
Friends, we are very happy to inform you
that if you join PolicyBazaar,
you will also be provided with a toll-free number and a special email ID,
which can be accessed at any time.
You can also resolve all your queries.
Apart from this, our team provides
you with a very experienced and dedicated
relationship manager
and the relationship manager will always be
very prompt in taking your work forward and will make
every
possible effort to grow your business by leaps and bounds according to a very good microsystem.
Friends, I am very happy to inform you that you are going to get
more products from Clear Insurance Company than the fight of the situation.
In the coming time, the products that you are going to have include lifetime
life insurance,
health insurance, investment plan, car
insurance, two-wheeler insurance, family insurance,
guaranteed return plans,
which is a product of Clear Life
Insurance Company, one crore
health insurance and Budh
Immortally by paying money, apart from this, child
insurance plan, retirement plan, group
health insurance, travel insurance, Kissa,
my friends, unit linked
insurance policy, cancer insurance.
Apart from this, the Clear
Commercial Vehicle Insurance, Taxed
Insurance and Householder Insurance which are available in the market are
guaranteed return insurance from Clear Insurance.
Apart from this, reports are all
You will also get products, friends.
Apart from this, the products on which you will need to pay more attention in the future include
property,
fire and burglary, power insurance,
group health insurance, apart from group life insurance, group
term life insurance,
this group health plan, apart from this,
professional deminatory risk and compensation
plan, fiber insurance, which is rapidly engulfing the
entire world. To avoid all these incidents, cyber crimes are rapidly engulfing the entire world.
Along with this product, director and officer,
flu
construction and this plant contractor
plan, plants in that loop,
countless products like this are going to come in your bag.
Friends, I
feel very proud to tell you that all
these products, all the product
information, all the product training, all the
production knowledge, are provided to you by our team at
off-cost price, within which you
can double your income, your work area, your business, your interest, your traffic, your family's golden dreams day and night. Friends, you are requested
that there is a very wonderful platform
for you where you can definitely do it.  You can enhance the glory of
this Zip with your dignity and respect.
Friends, if you express your desire to
work as Point of This Person Bankhedi of Policy Bazaar by joining our team,
then you are requested to call us
on the number appearing on our screen by sending a
copy of your PAN card, your name or your
surname and talk to us about a call back
where our team will give
you a to-do list of products and
benefits so that your
clientele, your friends,
all your future customers will be satisfied with your service and
help you in growing your business. Friends, with this
your friend takes your permission and also
prays that if you have come to our channel for the
first time, then subscribe to our channel and
press the bell button
so that all the upcoming important videos
come to you in the notification first.
Friends, the
best way for you to appreciate us and our team on YouTube is to like our videos.
If you like
and forward our videos, then
considering the same parameters correct, YouTube will share our
videos to more friends like you.  She
tries her best to show it to other needy friends as well and it will only
work with your blessings and love for our sister-in-law friends, so
friends, it is requested that while liking our video, please
ask us to press the bell button
so that we can keep bringing all the important videos to
you continuously without any interruption.
This friend of yours takes permission from you along with water. Jai Hind
friends, Bharat Mata ki